Dexter 1x07
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET-鬼柰훙珙
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Dexter
Season 1 Episode 7
previously on "dexter"...
It is my new friend.
When he broke into my apartment,
he took some time to get to know me
my life, my secrets.
Same as the others --no blood.
Somebody who was herelast night saw something.
They got a night watchman,
but we can't find him.
It's the guard -- tucci.
I think he's alive.
Taking tucciover to county.
Rudy here is gonna put
meback together again.
Yo,pretty boy,you're
stealing my thunder.
I don't know.
I just might have tofight you for this one.
How about you focus onwhether or not he was the
man you saw at the old hospitalthat night,mr. Perry?
It was difficult to tell.It was dark.
Florida prisons kick free
25,000 inmates a year.
I search for the ones who
think they beat the system,
like jeremy downs.
Jeremy got off easy.
To the coroner,the knife
strokes looked random,
but I saw the work
of a young virtuoso.
Are you gonna fuck me,faggot?
'Cause I killedthe
last guy who raped me.
I understand now.
Jeremy didn't murder
that boy four years ago.
He was taking out the garbage.
Wait,is that all?
디시인사이드 미국드라마 갤러리
딕테이션/한글번역 : 에스뷰
한글교정 : 글그린이™
싱크편집 : jimmy
Cirle of Friends
The fbi estimates that there are less than 50
serial killers active in the united states today.
FBI는 현재 미국 내에서 50 명이 안 되는
연쇄 살인범이 활동 중이라고 보고 있다
We don't get together at conventions,
우리는 집회를 하지도 않고
share trade secrets,or
exchange christmas cards...
크리스마스카드를 주고받지도 않으며
비밀을 공유하지도 않는다
but sometimes I wonder what
it's like for the others.
하지만 때로는 다른 살인범들은
어떨까 궁금해진다
The only sound I hear,
내가 듣는 소리는,
the only sound in the entire world...
세상에서 내가 듣는 소리는
...is my heart beating.
내 심장 뛰는 소리뿐이다
맹세컨대, 모건, 이 사건이 끝나면
네 녀석이 정신 진단을 받도록 만들겠어
I swear to christ,morgan,after this case,
I'm submitting your assfor
psychiatric evaluation.
전 그저 피가 뿌려진 패턴과
방향 각도를 재현해 보던 중이었어요
I'm just retracingcastoff patterns,
directionality angles.
Can you tell us what
happened here or not?
무슨 일이 일어난 건지
안다는 거야 모른다는 거야?
It's an execution.
처형식으로 살해됐어요 / 피살자는
장학생에다 졸업 앨범의 편집자였다는군
The kid's an honor student,
editor of his school yearbook.
It's all in the knife work.
칼자국을 보면 알 수 있어요
It's skillful,no wasted motion.
The killer had experience.
기술적이고, 감정적으로 주춤거리질
않았어요. 경험이 있다는 거죠
Every strokehit a major artery...
모든 칼자국이 주요 혈관이나
그 근처를 찔렀어요
or at least came close.
Are you getting a god
damn hard-on there,morgan?
뭐야, 이걸 보고 성적 흥분이라도 되는 거야?
No,it's truly horrific.
He was yearbook committee,you said?
정말 끔찍해요
졸업 앨범의 위원이라고 했죠?
내일까지 보고서 올리도록 해
I want your reporton this tomorrow.
내 가장 큰 장애는 덕스 경사라고
하고 싶지만 그는 아니다
I wish I could say sergeant doakes is my
biggest problem right now, but he's not.
이 상처를 본 적이 있다
I've seen these wounds before.
라구에타의 소파에다 침 흘리고 있잖아
You're droolingon laguerta's couch.
You pullinga midnight shift?
저녁 근무세요?
Lopez has the trots.
Why are you still here?
로페즈가 설사를 한대
- 자넨 왜 아직 여기 있어?
- 있으면 안 돼요?
Why not? Nothing at home except
an emptyfridge and an empty bed.
집에 가 봤자 빈 냉장고에 빈 침대뿐인데요
If I wasn't marriedand
10 years younger...
내가 결혼을 안 했고 10 살만 젊었어도...
I'd still be in high
school.Keep dreaming.
그럼 난 아직도 고등학생일걸요
꿈 깨세요
Wiseass.
냉동 트럭 킬러에 대한
단서를 조사 중이었어요
I've been chasing leadson
the ice-truck killer.
대부분 별 가능성은 없는 거지만요
Pathetic long shots,mostly.
Yeah?What kind of leads?
그래? 무슨 단서?
대량 살인에 관한 연구서를 봤는데요
바보 같은 일로 잡히게 되더라고요
I looked at the research.
With mass murderers,
it's dumbshit that trips them up.
Son of sam got a parking ticket
outside his own crime scene.
샘의 아들은 자신의 범행 현장 근처에서
주차 위반 딱지를 받았어요
So you ranparking violations
at the crime scenesof our guy?
그래서 우리 범인도
주차 위반 딱지를 먹었나 알아봤어?
Smart.
Yeah,but none of the registere
downers had criminal records.
그래요, 하지만 차 주인 중에서
전과 기록이 있는 사람은 없었어요
Try "moving violations."
그럼 운전 중 딱지 받은 걸 찾아봐
Timothy mcveigh drove waytoo
fast on the way out of town.
티모시 맥베이는 과속으로 딱지를 받았어
Neil perry --I know that name.
닐 페리, 아는 이름인데
Yeah,he came forwardas a
witness two weeks ago
맞아요, 2 주 전 토니 쿠치의 신체 조각이
버려질 때 목격자라고 찾아온 사람이에요
when pieces of tony tucciwere
showing up around town.
He rode through a stop sign two blocksfrom
the third crime scene at the seven seas motel.
세 번째 범행 장소인 세븐 시즈 모텔에서
두 블럭 떨어진 곳에서 정지 신호를
그냥 지나갔어
Why woulda voluntary witness
be at two separatecrime scenes?
목격자라고 자청한 사람이 어째서
서로 다른 두 곳의 범행 장소에 있었던 거지?
I don't know. Maybe he
waschopping up hookers.
글쎄요, 그자가 매춘부들을
절단한 건지도 모르죠
Holy mother of fuck,is this him?
- 아, 이런 제기랄 세상에, 이자일까요?
- 확인해 보자고
Let's find out.
- 확실히 이 주소가 맞아요?
- 차량국에 의하면 여기 산다고 돼 있어
Are you surethis is the right address?
According to dmv,this is where perry lives.
With his seven inbred
cousins,by the look of it.
꼴이 근친상간으로 낳은
사촌들도 같이 살 것 같아요
Somethinghas got to be wrong with
somebody that can livein a steel box.
이런 철상자 안에 산다는 게 정상은 아니야
Aluminum,actually.
이건 알루미늄이야
Nina and I hada deluxe multisectional.
니나하고 나는 칸이 나뉜
고급 모빌 홈에 살았어
진짜로요?
- For real?
- It was our starter home.
우리 첫 집이었어
범행에 쓰인 차예요
This is our car.
피살자 중 하나가 피살된 날, 나무 패널이
달린 왜건 차에 타는 게 목격됐어요
One of the victimswas seen getting in a wood-paneled
station wagon on the night of her death.
Let's take one step at a
time.Let's find our guy.
이봐 우선 하나씩 하자고
먼저 놈을 찾아야 돼
According to his files, he works
as a computer analystfor miami lake.
놈의 파일을 보면 마이애미 레이크에서
컴퓨터 분석가로 일하고 있어
Look up...slowly.
위를 봐요, 천천히요
자네가 앞문을 맡아, 모든
출입구를 커버해 난 뒤로 갈 테니
All right,take the front door.
Cover all the exits.
- I'm going to the back.
- ok
Open up,perry!It's the police!
문 열어 페리, 경찰이다
Open up,perry!Police!
경찰이다
Open up,perry!
Open the door!
문 열어
Hey,angel,I got him!
엔젤, 여기 있어요
경찰이다, 거기서
Wait!Stop running,perry!
Get the fuck down!
서지 못해!!
Fuck!
젠장맞을!
범인의 칼자국이 눈에 익다 했어
I knew I recognized the
knife work of the killer.
제레미 다운스
Jeremy downs.
I had him.
내가 죽이려던 놈
내 손아귀에 있었지
He was mine...
제레미가 죽인 건 자신을
강간한 놈이란 걸 알기 전까지
until I found out the boy
jeremy killed raped him...
*******
날 강간했어... 그래서
so I let jeremy go.
그래서 그 아일 놔줬다
It seemed fair.
그게 공평해 보였으니까
But my random act of kindness was misguided.
하지만 내 엉뚱한 친절함은 잘못된 거였다
내 본능대로 움직였다면, 이 고등학교
졸업 앨범의 편집자는 살아 있겠지
If I had followed my instincts,
this boy's high-school yearbook
would still have an editor.
the task force will tear apartthe house for any
evidence that links neil perryto the ice-truck murders.
특별 수사팀은 페리와 냉동 트럭 살인이
연관된 증거를 찾기 위해
집 안을 샅샅이 뒤져야 한다
We need proof this time,
people -- tangible proof.
이번엔 증거가 필요해, 확실한 증거가
What is it?
경찰이 냉동 트럭 킬러를
찾았다는 게 사실이야?
They really foundthe ice-truck killer?
내가 찾았어
I did.
그래요, 우리가 송환에 드는 경비를
지불할 거예요
Yes,yes.We will financially guaranteeex
tradition from anywhere. James?
제임스
Yeah,I'm on it,lieutenant.
I'll run the task force.
- 네, 반장님 제가 특별 수사팀을 지휘하죠
- 경사는 뒷골목의 고등학생 살인 사건을 맡아요
actuly I need you and pullman to stay
with the knife victimin the alley.
His parentsare high-profile.
부모가 유명인이거든
Hi, Whatever you need.
그래요, 반장님 말씀대로 하죠
Angel... you found perry.
You run the task force.
엔젤, 자네가 페리를 찾았으니
자네가 지휘를 하도록 하게
Contact the fugitive'sfriends,family,
가족이나, 친구, 직장 동료, 드럭 딜러
co-workers,coke dealer anybody
who might tryto hide him.
- 누구든 놈을 숨겨 줄 만한 사람을 찾아
- 사진을 돌릴까요?
You want usto circulate his photo?
In neighborhoods only.
Keep it away from the media.
이웃들에게만, 언론에 노출되지 않게
This case stays low-profile.
이 사건은 조용히 수사해야 돼
The last thing I need is
anothertony tucci on my hands.
또다시 토니 투치 같이 되선 안 돼
Anything else,lieutenant?
다른 건 없습니까?
Yes --choose task-force members who
can puttheir regular duties aside
팀 대원을 자네가 뽑도록 해
페리가 잡힐 때까지
모든 걸 걸 수 있는 대원들로, 알았지?
and bust ass untilneil
perry's apprehended.
- Okay
- Okay,that's all.Thank you.
도미닉
이상, 고마워
Do you really thinkthis is the guy?
- 이자가 진짜 범인이라고 생각해?
- 모든 게 맞아떨어져
It's all lining up.
I saw him,dex.I chased him.
내가 봤어, 놈을 쫓았다고
Debra morgan.
데브라 모건
이리 와, 자네도 팀원이야
Get over here.You're on the team.
- Do you hear that? I'm on the team.
- yeah
들었어? 나도 팀원이래
Do you think we get hats?
모자라도 주는 걸까?
Hardly looks a guycapable
of terrorizing miami.
이자는 마이애미를 공포로
몰아넣은 자 같이 안 보여
A science camp,maybe.
과학 캠프라면 모를까
난 간다, 새 소식이 있으면 알려 줄게
I'm off.I'll keep you in the loop.
Where's my blood report,sparky
- 내 보고서는 어찌 됐어, 스파키?
- 작성 중입니다
I'm on it,sergeant.
How you doing,mrs. Bennett?
안녕하세요, 미시즈 베넷?
Hey,charlie.Where are the kids?
우리 애들은요?
Your husband swung bya few
minutes ago. He didn't tell you?
남편 분이 몇 분 전에 오셨었는데요,
말 안 하던가요?
I never seen codylight
up like that before.
코디가 그렇게 환하게 웃는 건 처음 봤어요
Big treat --the old man coming down.
- 아빠가 직접 오니까...
- 잠깐, 잠깐만요, 폴 말인가요?
Wait,wait. Wait.Paul?
- 네, 방금 애들을 데려갔어요
- 애들을 폴이 데려가게 했다고요?
Yeah.He just picked up the kids.
You gave my childrento paul?
Are you stupid?
당신 바보 아니야?
I told the administrative officethat cody and
astor are not to be releasedinto his custody!
교무실에다가 애들을
애 아버지에게 맡기지 말라고 했는데
Well,nobody told me.
난 아무 얘기도 못 들었어요
He just got outof fucking jail!
폴은 방금 망할 감옥에서 나왔다고요!
Everyone,follow strict,sterile protocol.
모두들 정확하고 위생적인 절차에 따르도록 해
There will be no contamination
of my crime scene.
내 지휘 현장에서 오염은 있을 수 없어
Bag anything that could be used
to murder or disposeof a human body.
살인이나 사체 유기에 쓰였을
만한 거는 모두 담아 가도록 해
That's pretty mucheverything in here,boss.
그럼 여기 있는 거 다 담아야 하는데요
이거는 빼고요
Except this.
He's a sick fuck.
정말 구역질 나는 놈이에요
Some might say that.
그렇게 보는 사람도 있지만
To others,crypto-taxidermy is a fine art.
박제품을 예술품으로 보는 사람도 있어요
I got a mummifiedchupacabra at home.
우리 집에 박제된 추바카가 있어요
Can I have permissionto run masuka's
prints as the ice-truck killer?
마수카의 지문을 냉동 트럭 킬러로서
채취할 수 있도록 허락해 주실래요?
No need for that.
그럴 필요 없어, 지금 당장
따끈한 DNA를 줄 수 있어
I'll give yousome warm dna right now.
God,you're gross.
I didn't hear that.
윽, 토할 것 같아, 못 들은 걸로 할래요
Detective,I found something.
형사님, 뭔가 나왔습니다
An archive of hidden files.
숨겨 놓은 파일들이에요
A lot of how-to documents --
어떻게 소의 피를 뽑아내는가,
draining blood from cattle,
wartime amputation techniques.
전쟁 시 절단 테크닉,
"Butcheringthe human carcass"?
시체를 토막 내는 법
There's even an article about countries
thatdon't extradite to the U.S.
미국과 범인 인도 조약을 안 한
나라에 대한 기사도 있어
We got this fucker.
- 이거면 확실히 잡은 거죠
- 이건 아무것도 아니야
We got jack shit,morgan.
여기 있는 건 모두 상황 증거야
우린 확실한 증거가 필요해
Everything in hereis circumstantial.
We needsome hard evidence.
아직 다 본 건 아니잖아요, 안 그래요?
Hey,I'm not donelooking yet. Are you?
학교가 애들을 폴에게
데려가라고 할 권리는 없어
The school had no rightto
release my children to paul.
- No,they didn'T.
- He lost his custody rights
물론 없지
내 머리를 거실 벽에다 박았을
때부터 애들 양육권은 없는 거라고
right around the time my
headhit the living room wall.
I would think so.
그렇지
I-I should be outlooking for my kids.
- 밖에 나가서 애들을 찾아봐야겠어
- 리타, 전화가 올지도 모르니 여기서
Rita,the best thingyou could do for the
kids is stay herein case he tries to call.
기다리는 게 좋을 것 같아
전화를 안 하면?
What if he doesn't?
I mean,what if he kidnapped them to
get back at mefor putting him in jail?
자길 감옥에 보낸 거에 대한 보복으로
아이들을 납치라도 하려는 거면?
덱스터 난...
Dexter,I --
Hi.
Astor!
애스터!
엄마, 아빠가 집에 왔어
Mom,look -- it's dad.He came home.
Yeah.
그래
What,you think I wasgonna move to the moon?
아빠가 달나라라도 간 줄 알았어?
Stop it.Just stop.
그만 해요
Do you know I called the police?
내가 경찰에 연락한 거 알아요?
Why? I told you I was
taking them to the carnival.
- 왜? 애들을 카니발에 데려간다고 했잖아
- 언제요?
No,you didn'T.
Rita,I called youat the hotel.
호텔에 전화했더니 휴식 시간이라고 해서
They saidyou were on a break,
so I left a message withthe
info and my cell number.
내 휴대폰 번호하고 함께 메시지를 남겼는데
Uh,hi.How are you?
아, 안녕하세요
I'm paul bennett,father on parole.
난 폴 베넷이라고 해요
가석방된 애들 아버지요
Uh,dexter morgan.
덱스터 모건입니다
Uh,I can't thinkof anything clever to say.
별로 현명한 대꾸가 안 떠오르네요
폴, 이건 이러면 안 돼요
Paul,this is unacceptable.
I-I have custody. You can't just
take themwithout my permission.
양육권은 내게 있어요. 내 허락도
없이 애들을 데려갈 순 없다고요
난 내 애들을 보러온 거야
I cameto see my babies.
I missed them,rita.
애들이 보고 싶었어, 리타
생각나는 게 많았어
I missed a lot of things.
I should phone the station,
call off the dogs.
경찰에 전화를 할게
- 추적을 그만두라고 해야지
- 아저씨, 아빠가 집에 왔어
Dexter,look --my dad's home.
Yeah,I see that,buddy.
응, 그래 그렇구나
Hey,angel. You're the
experton manufactured living.
엔젤, 선배가 생활공간 전문가지
This closet looka little small to you?
이 옷장이 좀 작아 보이지 않아요?
A little.
조금
Sweet.
근사해
신문 기사들이에요
I've gotnewspaper articles.
토막 난 사체가 풀장에서 발견되다
"Dismembered bodyfound in a pool."
"Ice-truck killerappalls miami."
냉동 트럭 킬러가
마이애미를 공포에 떨게 하다
This is a recordof everything he's ever done.
- 자신이 한 일에 대한 기록이에요
- 이건 사진인데
I got photos.
- Did we release those photosto the press?
- No.
범행 현장 사진이에요
언론에 사진을 공개했나요?
아니
- Did he take them himself?
- He had to.
- 자신이 직접 찍었을까요?
- 그랬겠지
- Did we just hitthe mother lode?
- No.
방금 금광을 발견한 건가요?
아니, 젠장할 놈의 금광을 발견했어
We hit the motherfuckingmother lode.
Oh,my god
모빌 홈 안에서 증거물이 쏟아지고 있어요
the evidence just keep
spiling up at the mobile home.
I just authorized an
excavation of the back patio.
뜰도 파낼 수 있도록 허가를 했어요
거기에 뭔가 묻혀 있을 거라고 봐요
I think there's somethingburied there.
What are we doingto find neil perry?
페리를 찾기 위해선 어떤 조치를 취했나?
I put his name in the automated
system and notified e fbi.
자동 수사 시스템에 이름을
올렸고, FBI에 연락을 했어요
Airports on alert?
- 비행장에도 경고를 했나?
- 비행장, 기차역, 버스 정류소 모두요
Airports,train stations,bus lines.
We should trackhis credit cards.
- 그자의 신용카드도 주의해서 봐야 해
- 이미 해 놨어요, ATM과 은행 구좌도요
Already done,along with
A.T.M.Sand bank accounts.
I also put a tapon his home phone.
집 전화에 도청 장치도 했고요
Seems you thoughtof everything.
- 모든 걸 다 생각해 둔 것 같군
- 그런 것 같네요
It seems that way.
- Look,maria
- no need to apologize.
- 이봐, 마리아
- 사과하실 필요는 없어요
I don't require your approvalto do my job.
제 일을 하는데 서장님의 승인이
필요한 건 아니니까요
I know that.
알고 있어
I've been kicking your ass
'cause I knewyou had this in you.
자네에게 심하게 군 건 자네가 이런 성과를
거둘 능력이 있다고 믿었기 때문이야
Well,thank you for making
me the woman I am today.
감사합니다, 오늘의 제가
있게 해 주셔서요
I love you to everything.
엄마의 모든 걸 다 사랑해
I love youto everything,too.
나도 너의 모든 걸 사랑해
He's not gonnahit you anymore.
아빠가 더는 때리지 않을 거야
He told me at the carnival.
카니발에서 그랬어
내가 약속하라고 했어
I made him promise.
Thank you,baby.
고맙다 아가
I haven't had time to
process as much as the kids.
내겐 애들처럼 변할 시간이 없었어
I mean,paul was supposed to
belocked up for another year.
내 말은 폴은 아직 일 년은
더 갇혀 있어야 했거든
Cody seemsto be processing okay.
코디는 잘 적응한 것 같은데
Cody's too young.
코디는 아직 어려
A dad's just a concept
to him,not a person.
아빠라는 게 사람이라기보다
개념이었거든
But astor -- she remembers
what he put us through.
에스터는 폴이 무슨 짓을
했는지 기억하고 있어
Well,at leastyou're not married anymore.
지금은 적어도 부부는 아니잖아
That's just it.
바로 그거야
Technically,we are.
원칙적으로 부부인 상태야
When paul went to prison,
I started divorce proceedings,
폴이 감옥에 가고 나서
이혼 신청을 했는데
but he refusedto sign the paperwork.
사인을 안 하고 있어
As a power play?
힘 겨루기인가?
I don't think so.
아닌 것 같아
I think for all the
darkness that haunts him,
폴은 어둠에 쫓기기 때문에
가족을 갖고 싶어하는 거야
paul loves having a family.
I think he's just afraidto let go.
가족을 잃는 걸 두려워해
언제 처음 알아차렸어?
When did youfirst notice it?
This darknessinside
the guy you fell for.
당신이 사랑하는 사람 속에
어두운 기운이 있는 걸
I always knewit was there.
I guess I just didn't thinkI deserved better...
늘 알고 있었지만 난 더 좋은
사람을 만날 가치가 없다고 생각했어
당신을 만나기 전까진
till I met you.
I have a dark side,too.
나도 어두운 면이 있는데
What? I do.
왜? 나도 있다니까
Somehow I doubt that.
어째 믿기질 않는데
당신은 좋은 사람이야, 덱스터
You have a good heart,dexter.
폴 같지 않아, 당신은
사람들을 다치게 하지 않아
You're not like paul.
You don't hurt people.
Innocent people.
죄 없는 사람들
난 죄 없는 사람은 다치게 하지 않아
I don't hurtinnocent people.
이봐요, 볼링장은 코너를 돌아서예요
Hey,dude,the bowling
alley'saround the corner.
Hey,I'm lookingfor jeremy downs.
이봐, 제레미 다운스를 찾는데
제레미?
Jeremy?
여기서 나갔어요!
He vacatedthe premises!
Focus.
잘 들어, 제레미를 찾고 있다고
I'm trying to find jeremy.
Oh,I get it.
아, 알겠다
Look,man,I'm not
reallyinto that homo shit,
있잖아요, 난 호모 같은 거 아니지만
but I'm kind of shorton money for weed,
내가 대마초 살 돈이 모자라서 그러는데
so I guess I'll do it for
lessthan jeremy's charging.
제레미보다 조금 싸게 해 줄게요
Wait.What does jeremy charge?
잠깐, 제레미는 얼마나 받아요?
Jeremy's selling himself?
제레미가 자신을 팔고 있어?
I mean,he's always hanging outwith the
brokeback boys down at flamingo park.
늘 플라밍고 공원에서 브록백(게이)
애들하고 같이 어울리고
Comes backwith fistfuls of cash.
돌아올 땐 돈을 한 움큼씩
갖고 오는데요
나야, 닐 페리네 집으로 당장 와
이걸 봐야만 해
It's me. Get your ass overto neil perry's place.
You're gonnawant to see this.
Deb,it's my day off.
뎁, 오늘은 내 월차야
Just get your ass over here.
어서 오라고,
We're about to bust open the
goods on the ice-truck killer.
곧 냉동 트럭 킬러의
보물 창고가 열릴 거야
Not what I expected.
예상 밖인데
So lifelike.
꼭 살아 있는 것 같아
Hey,dex.
오빠
I thoughtyou'd want to be here.
여기 있고 싶을 거라고 생각했어
Something's buried down there.
Masuka's been digging all night.
저기 뭔가가 묻혀 있어
마수카가 밤새 파내고 있는 중이야
I hate to break thisto you,deb,
이런 말 하긴 싫지만, 뎁
사람을 잘못 찾은 거 알고 있지?
but you know you've got
the wrong guy here,right?
The ice-truck killer drains
the blood from his victims,
냉동 트럭 킬러는 피를 다 빼내고
냉동을 시킨 후, 그제야 관절을 절단해
freezes their bodies,
and only then severstheir limbs.
It's clean and efficient
his psychological signature.
깨끗하고 효과적이지
그게 놈의 정신적 서명이야
반면에 닐 페리는 길에서
죽은 걸 박제해 두고 있어
Neil perry,on the other
hand,stuffs roadkill.
Yeah,and turns it into
fucked-up fantasy shit.
그래, 그게 놈의 환상 놀이라는 거야
But the fantasiesare all wrong.
그 환상들이 전부 잘못된 거라니까
The guy we're looking
for wouldn't turn dead,
우리가 찾는 범인은 저런 더러운
죽은 것들을 생생한 만화같이
dirty things into living cartoons.
He'd find that pathetic.
모아 두진 않을 거라고
비참하다고 할걸
How do you know?
어떻게 알아
Because it is pathetic.
왜냐하면 비참해 보이잖아
뎁, 내 말을 믿어
Deb,trust me.
Neil perry is not a killer.
닐 페리는 살인자가 아니야
He's a dabbler.He's a waste of time.
놈은 취미가 저런 거야
시간 낭비라고
우리가 찾는 범인의 어렸을 때 환상이
동물을 죽이는 거였어도 묻어 버렸지,
If the guy we're looking for took
his early fantasies outon animals,
he'd bury them. *************
- 진열해 놓지는 않았을 거야
- 일찍이 사람을 죽인 거는?
And want aboutan early human kill?
Wod he bury that,too?
그것도 묻어 버렸을까?
Sure. Probably.
- 그래, 물론이야
- 그럼 뒤를 봐
En turn around.
You were saying?
방금 뭐라고 했지?
It looks likean adult female.
성인 여자처럼 보이는군
Any idea how longthe
body's been down there?
얼마나 묻혀 있었는지 알 수 있겠어?
Based on decomposition,
부패 정도로 보아서
죽은 지 2, 3 년 정도요
she's been tits upfor two,
maybe three years.
We'll know moreafter the autopsy.
부검을 해 보면
좀 더 알 수 있을 거예요
What happened to the limbs?
Did they rot off?
거기 다리는 왜 그런 거죠?
썩어서 떨어진 건가요?
아니, 깨끗이 절단된 거야
No. They're clean cuts.
But he didn't chop upthe whole body.
하지만 온몸을 절단하지는 않았어
아마도 페리의 첫 번째 살인이겠지
This could beperry's first kill,
like he was experimenting.
실험을 한 것처럼 말이야
You're the expert,dex.
What do you thk?
오빠가 전문이잖아
어떻게 생각해?
Sure. Sounds good.
그래, 좋아 보이네
Actually,it sounds perfectly awful.
사실은 끔찍하다
For weeks,I've felt like a
student in a master class.
몇 주 동안 난 매스터 클래스에
있는 학생 같은 기분이었다
Is it really possible that
the master's on the run?
매스터가 도망 중이라니
가능한 일인가?
And even more tragic,
does he live in a double-wide?
더 끔직한 건 이런 데서
살고 있었다는 거다
(더블 와이드 모빌 홈)
The gravitrongoes so fast,mom.
그라비트론이 너무 빨리 달려서
My dad took me on itthree times.
아빠가 세 번이나 태워 줬어
그랬어?
Wow.Is that so?
All right,let mecut you
guys up some fruit.
엄마가 과일 잘라 줄게
Astor wouldn't go.She was afraid.
누나는 안 타겠다고 했어
무섭대
So what?I don't like fast rides.
뭐 어때?
난 빨리 달리는 것 싫어해
Hello?
누구세요?
- Who wants doughnuts?
- I do.
도넛 먹고 싶은 사람?
저요
Paul,you can't just walk
in here whenever you want.
폴, 이렇게 막 들어오면 안 돼요
You don't live hereanymore.
당신은 여기 사는 게 아니잖아요
아, 미안해, 옛날 버릇이라서
Oh. Sorry about that.Old habits.
I'll ring the doorbellnext time.
다음엔 벨을 누를게
I got these for you.
이건 당신 거야
알았어, 여기 아무데나 놓지 뭐
All right. I'll just put
them in,uh,something.
Dad,can I havea doughnut?
아빠, 도넛 먹어도 돼?
You got it,buddy.Coming up.
그럼, 내가 줄게
What,n-now you're making
me out mto be the bad guy?
이제 날 나쁜 엄마를 만들려고 그래요?
They haven'thad breakfast yet.
애들은 아직 아침도 안 먹었어요
You know what? Kidlet,
my bad.Sorry about that.
있잖아, 얘들아
아빠가 잘못했어
이 도넛은 학교 갔다 와서 먹자
These doughnutsare for after school.
대신 아빠가 계란 프라이와
팬케익을 만들어 주지 / 폴!
But I could whip up
some eggs and pancakes.
- Paul!
- Very little syrup,I promise.
시럽은 조금만 치고
- And meat.You into neat?
- Uh-huh.
고기는?
고기 좋아해?
I like meat on my feet.
It's real squishy.
내 발에 고기를 덮는 걸 좋아해
질퍽거리잖아
Paul.
폴, 이러면 안 돼요
You can't do thisanymore,paul.
What?! What?!
뭐? 뭘?
Help raise my kids?!
내 아이들 키우는 걸 돕겠다는데
Yes,I can.That's my job.
왜 안 돼, 그게 내 일인데
이봐
All right,look.
여자 혼자 아이를 키우는 게 얼마나
I-I can't evenbegin to understand
how difficult this has beenfor you,
힘든지 이해를 한다고
말할 수 없는 거 알아
rita, being a single mom,okay?
그래서 정말 미안해
A-and for that,I-I'm eternally sorry.
I let you down.
당신을 실망시켰어
I let everybody down.
모두를 실망시켰다고
But if I could justfind that frying pan.
하지만 프라이팬만 있다면, 애스터
Astor...
프라이팬 찾는 것 좀 도와 줄래?
want to help mefind the frying pan?
닐 페리의 프로파일이 나왔어
We got a profile of neil perry.
컴퓨터 전문가이고
He's a computer expert.
아이큐는 아주 높아
혼자 있길 좋아하고, 전과는 없으며
I.Q. -- Off the chart.
He's a loner,no priors.
His father split when he was 6.
아버지는 닐이 6 살 때 없어졌고
His motherwas an alcoholic,abusive,
엄마는 알콜중독에 가해자였고
놈의 첫 번째 희생자일 가능성이 높아
and possibly his first victim.
로베타 페리, 치과 기록에 의하면
땅에서 나온 게 로베타야
Roberta perry.
Dental records say she was
the one under the patio.
Now,neil kept her death quiet by cashing her
social-security checks for the last twyears,
닐은 엄마의 죽음을 속이고 지난
2 년간 엄마의 연금 수표를 받아 챙겼어
but he did not kill her for the money.
하지만 돈 때문에 죽인 건 아니야
Morgan?
모건
We think he wanted release.
우리 생각엔 놈이 자유로워지고 싶었다고 봐요
Roberta perryran her son's life,
로베타는 아들의 삶을 좌지우지했어요
controlled him,beat him as a kid.
아들을 조정했고, 학대했어요
We think he dreamtabout
killing her for years.
아마 오랜동안
엄마를 죽이고 싶어했을 거예요
I just spoke with perry's
cellphone provider.
방금 페리의 휴대폰 회사와 통화를 했는데
Can they track his location?
놈이 있는 곳이 추적됐나?
No signal, he probably
turned off his phone.
신호가 사라졌대요, 전화를 꺼 놨을 거예요
But,according to records,
하지만 냉동 트럭 킬러의 피살자가
he used it on some of the nights
the ice-truck killer victimswere taken.
납치된 날 통화한 기록이 있어요
Who did he call?
누구에게 걸었죠?
음성 사서함, 메시지 확인 등이야
Voice mail,mostly,checking messages.
버라이즌(전화 회사)이 삼각법(三角法)을 쓴
결과 한 군데서 건 걸로 좁혀졌어요
Verizon triangulatedthe location.
All the calls camefrom the same place --
a six-block areaon southwest 8th street.
8 번가의 남서쪽 여섯째 블럭이에요
yeah,The tamiami trail.
태미애미 트레일 이에요
그 구역은 '묻지 마' 모텔들로 꽉 차 있어요
매춘부들의 영업장소죠
That strip'sfull of no-tell motels.
It's like a happyhunting ground for hookers.
There's a good chance that's
where he's killing his victims.
거기가 놈이 살인을 한
장소일 가능성이 높아
Let's recanvass the areafor leads.
자, 단서를 잡기 위해
그곳을 다시 수색해 보자
Now that we've gota photo of this guy,
이번엔 사진이 있으니
봤다는 사람이 나올 수도 있어
maybe we can find somebodywho actually saw him.
자 가자고
Let's go.
You're startingto look like her.
점점 반장님을 닮아 가요
집에 들러서 가족을 보고 갈래요?
Want to stop by your house,
check in with the family?
I'd rather check inwith your brother.
차라리 자네 오빠를 보고 가지
His instincts are usually
pretty good on this stuff.
이런 일엔 보통 덱스터의
직감이 아주 잘 맞거든
Yeah,not today.He'd
just piss on our parade.
오늘은 아니에요
우리 기분을 망치기나 할걸요
He needs his day off.
하루 쉬게 놔둬요
내가 처음 그의 작품을 봤을 땐
The first time I saw his work,
I felt like a spanish explorer landing
of the shores of the new world.
신세계에 발을 디딘
스페인의 탐험가 같은 기분이었다
No blood in the victims,
피도 없고, 핏자국도 없고
얼룩도 없다
no spatter,no stain.
Deb is wrong about him.
뎁이 잘못 안 거다
괜찮다
실수는 나도 했다
It's okay. Hell,I've made mistakes.
지금 난 큰 실수를 바로잡으려는 참이다
In fact,I'm about to
correct a big one right now.
Jeremy downs.
제레미 다운스
Hey,you want company?
봐요, 친구가 필요해요?
Just keep walkingand looking ahead.
그냥 걸어가, 앞을 보면서
호수 옆에 홍수림이 있어요
거기로 가면 돼요
There's some mangrovesover by
the lake. We can go in there.
It's too public.My car's
in the parking lot.
너무 공개된 장소야
내 차가 주차장에 있어
Are your windows tinted?
- 자동차 유리가 선팅됐어요?
- 앞을 보라고 했지!
I said,"eyes front."
무슨 일이야?
What's wrong?
Shit. Shit.
젠장, 젠장맞을!
앞에서 비켜!
Get the fuck out of my way!
Take it easy,jeremy!
Stay right there!
진정해, 제레미
거기서 꼼짝 마
Take him down!Take him down!
놈을 잡아, 쓰러뜨려
Hands behind your back.
손 뒤로 해
Stand up!Stand up!
일어서
Pink motel
Miami metro P.D.
Can we have a minute?
마이애미 메트로 경찰입니다
잠깐 시간 좀 내주세요
- 네
- 이 사람 본 적 있어요?
Yeah.
This guy look familiar?
I don't know.
글쎄요
오고 가고 하니까, 알잖아요
They come. They go.You get it?
기분 내러요
They "come."
이봐요, 돌아다니느라
발이 아파 죽겠어요
Look,my feet are aching
from pounding the pavement.
도와 줄 생각이 있기는 한 거예요?
You thinkyou could help us out?
이름이 뭐예요?
What's your name?
Laline consuelo garci* gixez.
라니나 콘수엘라 라센가르시아 고모
Laline...
라니나
oxzghte del hombre que
le dicen el ice-truck killer?
냉동 트럭 킬러에 대해서 알죠?
네
S?
Puede ser el.
????
So let's try this again.
그럼 다시 물을게요
Have you seen this man?
이 사람 본 적 있어요?
He's a regular. Rents a
roomby the month -- cash.
단골손님이에요
방을 한 달 단위로 빌리죠, 현금으로요
- 마지막으로 온 게 언제였죠?
- 지금 여기 있어요
When was the last timehe was here?
He's here now. He brought a
girl to his roomthis morning.
- 아침에 여자를 데리고 들어갔어요
- 매춘부 말인가요?
A working girl? A hooker?
- 그자 손님은 다..
- 방 번호가 뭔가요?
- who has to guess
- What's the room number?
- 20호요, 여기 마스터 키요
- 지원 요청해
20. Here's the master.
Call for backup. Let's hope
this girlis still alive.
여자가 아직 살아 있길 바라자고
- 지원팀을 기다려야 하나요?
- 희생자가 안에 있는데 아니지
Do we wait for tactical?
yeah, Not with a
possible victimin there.
이상 없어
Clear.
It's okay. We're here now.You're safe.
괜찮아요, 우리가 왔으니
안심하세요
Please get me out hurry,
before he comes back!
제발요, 여기서 나가게 해 줘요
그자가 오기 전에요
Where is he?
- 그잔 어디 갔나요?
- 나가게 해 줘요
Please,I want to get out!
그잔 어디 갔어요?
Where was he going?
The liquor store.He said
he's coming right back.
편의점에요
금방 온다고 했어요
왜 그래요?
What?
Hey,where's doakes? He paged me.
덕스 어딨어요?
찾았다고 들었는데
We need your reportfrom
that kid in the alley.
그 뒷골목 피살자에
관한 보고서가 필요해
But it's my day off. I was just
at don shula'sfamous golf course.
오늘 난 휴가예요
유명한 던 슐라 골프장에서
9번홀(back 9)을 치고 있었다고요
Did you finishyour report or not?
보고서 작성은 끝났어?
Yeah,it's in my lab.
네, 내 책상 위에 있어요
Wait.
이봐, 난 네가 한 일을 알고 있어
I'm on to you.
Excuse me?
뭐라고요?
골목에서 미친놈처럼 칼을 휘둘러 댔지
Your crazy-ass,knife-slashing
two-step in the alley.
자네 말이 맞았어
You were right.
You said the killerhad
previous experience. He did.
살인범이 경험이 있다고 했지
있었어
Oh. Really?
그래요?
마수카가 골목에서 채취한 지문이
미성년 범죄자의 것과 일치했어
Masuka lifted a printfrom the
alley that matched a kidfrom juvie.
Cut up a victim five years ago.
Same knife technique.
5 년 전에 칼로 난자해 죽였어
같은 방법으로 말이야
We just grabbed himat flamin go park.
방금 플라밍고 공원에서 잡았어
Great work,sergeant.
- 잘하셨네요, 경사님
- 그래, 자네 직감은 아주 정확해
Yeah.Your instincts were dead-on.
They're always dead-onwhen it
comes to killers. Why is that?
살인범에 관한 한 언제나 아주 정확하지
어째서지?
I'll just go getthat report.
가서 보고서나 가져올게요
I'm watching you.
내가 지켜보고 있어
보고 싶었어?
Miss me?
경찰이다
Police.On the ground.
땅에 엎드려, 천천히 말이야
Get down slowly.
Now the day is over
night is drawing nigh
get down!
엎드려
The shadows of the evening
steal across the sky
shadow of the evening
steal accross the sky
I said get the fuck down!
엎드리라고 했지
Now the darkness gathers
now the darkness gathered
facedown ,let's go!
어서
i begin to peep
birds and beasts and
flowers soon will be asleep
birds and bees and flowers
soon will be asleep
내 잡탕물에 뭘 더 넣고 싶어?
what else do you want to
put in the concoction?
Gummi bears.
거미 베어(젤리)
How do you two plan to eat
that,spread it on toast?
그걸 어떻게 먹으려고?
토스트 위에 발라 먹을래?
It alreadyhas toast in it.
안에다 토스트 넣었어요
Sot does.
정말 그러네
Keep mashing.I'll get the door.
계속 으깨, 누구 왔나 가 볼게
아, 안녕하시오
Oh.Hey,there,big guy.
Uh,dexter,right?
덱스터, 맞죠?
Paul,hi.Rita's not here.
폴, 안녕하세요
리타는 집에 없는데요
Oh,that's okay.I'm
actually here for the kids.
괜찮아요, 애들 보러 온 거니까
I came to dazzle
them with my booty.
상품으로 애들을 기쁘게 해 주려고요
This booty.
이 상품 말이오
아, 이건 좀 어색한데요
This is awkward.
I'm afraid I'm not comfortable letting
you inside the housewithout rita here.
리타가 없는데 당신을 집에
들여놓기가 거북해요
당신이 뭐, 베이비시터라도 되나?
Who are you,anyway,
like,the babysitter?
I'm watching the kidsright now,
지금은 내가 애들을 보고 있으니
so I suppose that
makes me the baby sitter.
베이비시터라고 할 수 있죠
Are you fucking my wife?
내 아내와 자는 거야?
I'll let rita knowyou stopped by.
다녀갔다고 리타에게 말하죠
Or I could just walk in.It's my house.
아니면 내가 그냥 들어갈 수도 있지
내 집이니까, 리타가 그 말은 안 했나 봐
I own this place. I bet she
didn't tell you that,did she?
아, 집주인...그런 건 내 소관이 아니라서
Homeowner issuesare way over my head.
차라리 경찰에 전화를 해서
처리를 하라고 하죠, 뭐
I should probablyjust call the
police, let them sort this out.
- Is that it?
- Yeah.
그게 답니까?
그래요, 이것 좀 애들에게 전해 주쇼
Yeah,why don't yougive those presents
to my little bucketsof sunshine,
그리고 리타에게 난 모터 코트에
묵고 있다고 해줘요
tell rita she can reach
meat the motor court?
Okay.
아내를 패는 마약 중독자지만
애들은 포기하지 않으려 하는군
He might be a crack-addled,
wife-abusing yahoo,
but he refuses to abandon his kids.
I'm not sure that's a good thing.
좋은 일인지 모르겠다
Take him on in.I'll be right there.
안에 데려가, 곧 갈 테니
You got it.
Congratulations.
축하해, 플로리다 역사상 가장
악명 높은 살인범을 잡았어
You just brought downthe most notorious
serial killer in florida history.
Fucking "A."He's in booking right now.
최고예요
지금 구금 기록 중이에요
It sucksyou weren't a part of this.
경사님이 팀원이 아니라니 말도 안 돼요
I mean,you and me -- we
pavedthe way for this,right?
사실 우리 둘이 길을
닦은 거잖아요, 안 그래요?
I'm cool.I've got my own bad guy.
난 괜찮아, 나도 나쁜 놈 하나 잡았잖아
방금 토니 투치의 메시지 받았는데요
Listen,I just picked up a
message from tony tucci.
Our favoritefun-loving amputee's
getting out of the hospital.
우리의 놀기 좋아하는
불구 아저씨가 퇴원한대요
There's a party tonight.
오늘 파티한대요
- No,thanks.
- I don't want to go,either.
사양하겠어
나도 가기 싫어요
하지만 손발이 잘렸잖아요
But the guy lost body parts,
and we get to tell himwe caught the guy.
범인을 잡았다고 알려 줘야죠
뭐 달리 할일이라도 있어요?
come on, What else you got going on?
Wouldn't you like to know?
뭘 그렇게 알려고 해?
There will be hookers there.
거기 가면 매춘부도 있을 텐데요
All right.Fine,mr. Grumpy
head. Have it your way.
알았어요, 무뚝뚝한 아저씨
맘대로 하세요
Did he threaten you?
폴이 위협을 했어?
No.Nothing like that.
아니, 그냥 자기 구역이란 걸 과시한 거지
He was justmarking his territory.
Fucking bastard.
개새끼!
Only you could make
those words cute.
그런 말도 귀엽게 들리네
Stop it.
그만 해
Paul said he owns this
house. Is that true?
폴이 이 집 소유주라는데 정말이야?
Yeah. Yeah.
응, 우리가 만나기 전부터 소유했어
He had it before we met.
I think he got it in a drug trade.
마약 거래로 받은 건가 봐
Dex,what am I gonna do?
대체 내가 뭘 해야 하지?
I'd startby getting a divorce.
이혼부터 해야지
당신을 이런 진창으로 끌어들였어
God,this is such a mess,
and I've dragged you into it.
There,there.
괜찮아
I just wish... I just wish he'd go away.
그자가 없어져 버렸으면 좋겠어
Why can't he just go away
and disappear forever?
그냥 영원히 어디론가 사라져서
안 나타날 수는 없을까?
He can do that
그럴 수 있지
very easily.
아주 쉽게
Fuck.
젠장
- We...we need to talk.
- Yeah.
얘기 좀 해요
그래, 바닥에 떨어진 내 심장부터 줍고
Just let me grab my heart
up off the fucking floor.
Holy fuck,rita.Whew.
Come on in.
들어와
Uh,no. No,I-I'm good right here.
아니, 아녜요. 여기가 좋아요
Aw,come on.
그러지 말고 들어와
Don't be that way.Come on in.
I got a six-pack
chilling in the cooler.
시원한 맥주도 있어
No.
아뇨, 더는요
No more.
What?
뭐가?
No more surprise
visits to the house,
더는 안 돼요
갑자기 찾아오지도 말고
내 친구를 위협하지도 말고
no more intimidatingmy friends,
and especiallyno more disney dad.
특히 좋은 아빠 노릇은
절대 안 돼요
You lost your rightto be a father
when you beatyour children's mother.
당신이 애들 엄마를 때리는 순간
애들 아빠라는 권리를 잃은 거예요
If you want to get to
know a stor and cody,
애스터와 코디를 만나고 싶다면
you're gonna have to
work for that privilege.
그 특권을 누릴 수 있도록
노력을 해야 될 거예요
Whoa,whoa,babe,can I get a word in here?
나도 한마디 해도 돼?
No.
아뇨
이혼 서류예요
Divorce papers.
They're the ones you
refused to sign in prison.
감옥에서 당신이 사인하기를 거부했던
Sign them now, and I'll agree
to supervisedvisits twice a week.
지금 사인을 하면 일주일에 두 번은
감독 하에 애들을 만나게 해 주겠어요
Show me you can do that for
six months,and then maybe --
그렇게 6 개월을 잘 지내면
어쩌면, 어쩌면
maybe -- I'll think about a
nonsupervised schedule.
감독 없이 만나게 해 줄 수도 있어요
Is this some kindof joke,rita?
뭐야, 농담하나?
You think you can really
make me back down?
정말로 날 포기하게 할 수 있다고 생각해?
No,I don'T.
아요, 하지만
내가 달리 뭘 할 수 있겠어요?
But what elseam I gonna do,paul?
A judge put me in control.
I'm in control now,
판사가 내게 조정권을 줬어요
내가 조정을 할 수 있다고요
and I have the power to make sure
you never seeyour children again
그러니 당신이 내가 하라는 대로 안 하면
내게는 당신이 애들을 평생
못 만나게 할 권리가 있어요
unless you doexactly as I tell you.
Goddamn,you are fine
when you're mad.
이런, 화가 난 당신은 멋져
I love the new you.
새로운 당신이 정말 사랑스러워
내가 잘못을 했으니 벌을 받아야지
I do.My ass is yours to kick.
I deserve it.Here -- look.
당연히 받아야 해
이봐, 난 변했어
Rita,I'm a changed man,
and I swear to god --
그런 날 당신에게 보여 주겠어
I am going to
prove it to you.
All right. There she is.
- 반장이야
- 시작이네
Anybodybring any popcorn?
팝콘 갖고 온 사람 없어?
You got him.
잡았군요
Both of them.
둘 다
Where's perry's lawyer?
페리의 변호사는 어딨어요?
He waived the right.
거부했어
I can't hear a thing.
Who's got the remote?
하나도 안 들려, 리모콘 어딨어?
There they are
my two colleagues...
저기 있다, 나의 두 동료가
엄밀히 말하자면
technically speaking.
다행이도 둘 중 하나는 가짜다
Thankfully,one of
them's a fraud.
Because you assume that.
당신들은 내가 살인을 했다고 추측하지
추측이라면 얼마든지 해
So you can assumeI killed them.
You can assume
anything that you want.
The doeris merely a fiction
that's added to the deed --the deed.
여기에 살인자는 없어
없는 걸 살인에 끼워 넣는군
살인, 물론 그건 진짜지
The deed is everything.
At least I hope he's a fraud.
적어도 난 그가 가짜이길 바란다
내 손에게 건배
Here's to my new hand.
사람들은 용기가 두려워할 줄
아는 사람만 갖고 있다고 하죠
Some say bravery is being the
only one who knows you're afraid.
내가 많은 불구를 치료했는데
But I've worked with a lot
of amputees,and I got to say --
난 토니 이분이 두려워할 줄
몰랐다고 생각해요
I don't thinktony
knew he was afraid.
Here's to one crazy bastard.
여기 완전히 제정신이
아니었던 분을 위해서
내 위축된 엉덩이에 키스를
Kiss my atrophied ass.
Now for the main event.
자 이제 메인 이벤트입니다
Medical marijuana?
의약용 대마초인가요?
You wish.
그랬으면 좋겠죠?
Can you,uh,help me
out here,rudy?
이것 좀 도와 줄래요, 루디?
Look at that shit.
이것 좀 봐, 반은 사람이고
반은 기계네
Half human,half machine.
But all man,baby.
하지만 전부 남자예요
내가 할게
May I have this dance?
춤 한번 출까?
Hey,buddy,you might havea
chance with me,after all.
이봐, 내게도 기회를 줘야죠
Oh,don't worry. There's still
plenty enoughof me to go around.
걱정 마요, 나중에 다 차례가 돌아갈 테니
So,you madethat hand and foot?
당신이 저 손발을 만들었어요?
네
좋은 일을 하셨어요
You did a good thing.
Tony lost a piece of himself,
토니는 자신의 일부를 잃었고
and I helped him find it.
난 그걸 찾아 준 거예요
살면서 딴 사람을 완전하게 만들어 줄
기회가 얼마나 되겠어요?
I mean,how often in life do you
get to make someone whole?
I wouldn't know.
글쎄요
It's like living art --what you do.
마치 살아있는 예술
같아요, 하시는 일이
It's funnyyou should say that,
because beforeI turned to prosthetics,
그런 말을 들으니 말인데,
사실 외과 보철학을 하기 전에는
I,uh,studiedthe human form at
the university of paris --sorbonne.
소르본 대학에서
인간의 형상을 공부했어요
- 정말요?
- 네
- Really?
- Yeah.
Have you had dinner yet?
- 아직 저녁 안 드셨죠?
- 먹었으면 좋겠어요
I would love to.
Uh,I thought I'd come
and show my support.
나도 와야겠다 싶어서
타이밍이 안 좋았나?
Bad timing?
No. No.
아니, 아녜요
Um,have some champagne,sergeant.
샴페인 좀 드세요
블로그, 팟 캐스트 등 정보는 끊임없이
See,we got blogs.
We got podcasts. You know,
the information won't stop.
It comes into your headand bleeds out your eyes,
뇌로 들어갔다가 나오죠, 모두 쓰레기예요
and it's all crap,you know?
요즘은 사람들의 관심을 끌기 위해선
See,you got to darefor greatness
these days to get people's attention.
아주 큰 일을 저질러야 해요
Did I get yours?
내가 당신 관심을 끌고 있나요?
This is worse than foreplay.
Why doesn't she ask himany questions?
이건 전희보다 더 지겹네
왜 아무것도 안 물어 보지?
I have no ideawhat she's doing,
but my patienceis wearing thin.
라구에타가 뭘 하는지 모르겠지만
점점 기다리기 힘들어지는군
I gave jeremy a chance,
and he blew it.
제레미에게 기회를 줬는데
녀석이 망쳐 버린 거다
Is this one going to
disappoint me,too?
이 녀석도 날 실망시킬 것인가?
That's an interesting
interview technique.
인터뷰 방식이 꽤 흥미롭군요
I'm tiredof asking questions.
난 물어 보는데 질렸어
You're getting off on
this too fucking much.
넌 여기서 얻어 가는 게 너무 많아
- Getting off on what?
- The game.
무엇으로부터 얻어 가죠?
게임이지
I'm guessing that's why you
didn't request a lawyer --
내 생각엔 그게 당신이 변호사를
요청하지 않은 이유라고 봐
so you can sit here and say
whatever shitcomes into your head.
여기 앉아서 하고 싶은 말은
뭐든 다 지껄이고 있지
Meanwhile,my assis
spreading like cheez whiz,
그 와중에 난 네가 지금 이건 쓸모없는
waiting for you to figure
out this isn't the fun part.
부분이라는 걸 알아차리길 기다리느라
내 엉덩이가 녹아날 지경이야
What are youtalking about?
무슨 소리예요?
We got you dead to rights.
넌 꼼짝없이 잡힌 거야
But the good timeswon't
start rolling
하지만 진짜 재밌는 시간은
네가 법정에 앉아 있고
till you're in a courtroom
with your ownpersonal judge ito
이토 판사가 재판관이 되어 카메라가
돌아가면서 시작이 되는 거야
and court tvcarrying
your scary-ass scowls
법정 티비(TV)에서는 너의 겁먹고 찡그린
얼굴이 생방송으로 나가게 되지
and crazy-shit live.
Fascination with serial
killersis an american pastime.
연쇄 살인범에 관심을 보내는 건
미국인들의 여가 활동이 됐어
You've got groupie housewives,
magazine profiles,
오빠 부대 주부들, 프로파일 잡지들,
블록버스터 영화
maybe even a summerblockbuster movie...
all waiting for you.
그 모든 게 널 기다리고 있어
But the feeding frenzy won't
start till you throw out the chum.
하지만 그런 관심은
네가 죄를 인정하고서야 시작되지
Until then,I'm just gonna chill.
그때까지 난 그냥 조용히 있는 거야
당신 말이 맞아
You're right.
Yeah.Is isn't the fun part.
이건 재미가 없어
The fun part... was
hanging themlike cattle.
소처럼 매달았을 때가 재미있었지
Hanging who?
누굴 매달았는데?
The hookers... right before
I cut their throats.
매춘부들
목을 자르기 직전에
Son of a bitch.
개자식
중력을 이용해 피가 다 빠져나가라고
거꾸로 매달았어
I used gravity rootsto hang them
upside down to drain the blood.
Then...
That shit is privileged.
The press nevergot ahold of that.
저건 언론에 내보내지 않은 정보야
...I'd pour in liquid nitrogento freeze
the blood before I cut them into nice,
액체 질소를 넣어서 피를 냉동시켰어
깔끔하게 절단하기 전에
- clean pieces.
- Yes.
See,you got to understand --I-I hate blood.
알겠지만, 난 피가 싫어
저기 그가 있다
And there it is --
내가 가졌던 모든 기대와 위대함이 주는
all the expectations I had,
모든 약속이 무너졌다
all the promises of
greatness wiped out.
My circle of friends is down to one.
내 친구는 이제 하나로 줄었다
How -- what are youdoing
here? Are you a cop?
어떻게?
여기서 뭐 하는 거예요?
경찰이에요?
The cameras are off.
I ve one minute.
카메라가 꺼진 건 1 분뿐이야
Tell me why.I need to know.
왜 그랬는지 말해 봐, 알아야겠어
뭘 왜 그래요?
- Why what?
- Don't!
정신차려
또 살인을 했어
You killed again.
I told you，I warned you don't
kill anyonewho doesn't deserve to die.
말했었지
경고했잖아, 무고한 사람은
죽여선 안 된다고
Why did you do it?
왜 그랬어?
To feel something different.
뭔가 다른 걸 느끼고 싶었어요
Different than what?
뭐랑 다른 걸?
What do you normally feel?
네가 평상시 느끼는 건 뭔데?
Nothing. Fucking nothing at all.
아무것도요
젠장맞을, 아무것도 안 느껴져요
I hate every fucking
god damn second of it.
그 모든 순간이 정말 싫어요
견딜 수가 없어요
I can't stand it --
living my life in my head.
머릿속으로만 삶을 산다는 거요
Does killingmake it better?
살인을 하니까 나아져?
아뇨, 더 나빠졌어요
No. Worse.
Fucking worse than ever.
더할 나위 없이 나빠졌어요
Put your handson the table.
테이블 위에 손을 올려놔
Do it.
어서
I'm a lot like you,you know?
나도 너와 많이 비슷해
Yeah,right.You're a killer?
아, 그래요?
당신도 살인자라고요?
I'm empty...
마음속이 비었다고
but I found a way to make
it feel less bottomless.
하지만 난 덜 공허하게
느끼는 방법을 찾았어
How?
어떻게요?
Pretend.
평범한 척하는 거지
You pretend the feeling
sare there for the world
감정이 있는 것처럼 하는 거야
세상을 위해서, 네 주변 사람들을 위해서
and for the peoplearound you.
알 게 뭐야, 어느 날 감정이 생겨날지
Who knows? Maybe one
day they will be.
What the hell are you doing,morgan?
- 여기서 뭐 하는 거야, 모건?
- 손톱 밑을 긁어내고 있었어요
I'm scraping under
the nails for blood.
Get out.
나가 봐, 이 쓰레기 같은 놈의 변호사가
오기 전에 10 분만 더 심문을 해야겠어
I want 10 more minuteswith this
piece of shit before his lawyer shows.
Stand up!
일어서
Living my life in my head --
머릿속으로 삶을 산다
제레미가 하는 말이
무슨 소리인지 나는 안다
I know exactly what jeremy means.
At least I had someone to talk to --
적어도 난 대화할 상대나 있었지
해리, 내 양아버지
harry,my foster father.
양아버지는 내게 살아남는 법을
가르치느라 수많은 시간을 보냈다
He spent endless hours
teaching me how to survive.
Excuse me,are you
jeremy downs' lawyer?
실례합니다, 제레미의 변호사인가요?
네, 그래요
Yes,I am. I'm just
heading over to see him.
제레미를 보러 가는 길입니다
Sooner would be better.
될 수 있는 한 빨리 가는 게 좋을 것 같네요
- Seriously.
- Thank you.
진짜로요
고마워요
내가 16 살 때 엄마가 죽었어요, 암으로요
My mom died when I was 16 --cancer --
and then it was just
me,my brother,my dad.
그때부터
나와 오빠와 아버지, 셋뿐이었죠
- 오빠가 있어요?
- 네, 덱스터예요
- You have a brother?
- Yeah. Dexter.
He and my dadwere really tight.
아버지와 오빠는 진짜 가까웠죠
둘이서 많은 시간을 함께 보냈어요
They were always
spending time together.
I guess I was jealous.
제가 좀 질투를 했죠
What,you mean you weren't
daddy's little girl?
당신은 아버지 사랑을 못 받았다고요?
No,I was,kind of.
그렇기는 했는데요
그냥 아버지는 오빠에게
특별한 관심이 있었어요
He just took a special
interest in dex,you know?
그래서 내가 경찰이 된 것 같아요
아버지가 경찰이었거든요
I think that's whyI became
a cop. That's what he was.
I thought maybe he would give
me more attention or something.
그러면 아버지의 관심을
더 받을 거라 생각했나 봐요
And did he?
그랬나요?
Not really...
별로요
but we had our moments.
하지만 우리도 좋은 때가 있었어요
당신은 어때요?
What about you?
How'd you become...
당신은 어떻게 해서 후크 선장이 됐죠?
captain hook?
Well,when I was little,
my mom got in a car accident,
내가 어렸을 때
엄마한테 차 사고가 났어요
and she lost both her legs.
두 다리를 잃었죠
That's terrible.
끔찍하네요
I rememberwhen it happened,
사고가 났을 때
I just wanted to
put herback together...
난 그저 엄마가 다시 온전했으면 했어요
you know,like humpty-dumpty,
하지만 회복 불능이었죠
just the pieces weren't around.
그냥 일부가 없었죠
내 놀이 친구들이 그리울 거다
I'm going to miss my playmate.
Sure,there's rita and the kids,
물론 리타와 아이들이 있지만
but they don't know the real me.
그 들은 진정한 나를 모른다
They can never know the real me.
진정한 나를 알아서는 안 된다
And now the father is back.
애들 아버지도 돌아오고
Things have changed.
사정이 달라졌다
"냉동 트럭 킬러 용의자, 경찰에 잡히다"
Everything has changed.
모든 게 달라졌다
I always prided myself on
being an outsider, but now...
난 늘 내가 아웃사이더인 것에
자부심이 있었다
"십대 살인범 다시 체포되다"
하지만 지금은
타인과의 관계가 절실히 필요하다
I feel the need to connect with someone.
I saw myself in jeremy...
제레미 안에서 내 자신을 봤다
but instead of helping
him like harry helped me,
하지만 해리가 내게 도움을
줬던 것처럼 하기보다는
I gave him a piece of fortune-cookie
advice that he never even heard.
난 그 아이가 전혀
못 들어 본 충고를 해 줬다
I failed him.
난 그 아이를 실망시켰다
He deserves better...
그 아인 좀 더 좋은 조언가를 만나야 한다
and he'll get it from now on.
그리고 지금부터는 그렇게 될 것이다
I guess I was wrong.
내가 잘못 생각했나 보다
Jeremy did hear my advice.
제레미는 내 조언을 들은 것이다
He killed someone who deserves to die.
죽어 마땅한 사람을 죽인 것이다
페리에 관한 상황이 어떻게 되지?
What's the statuson perry?
지금 호송 중이에요
I'm having him transferredright now.
The D.A. Wants to keep himat
county, pending arraignment.
검사가 카운티 교도소에 두고 싶어해요
인정 심리를 기다리는 동안에요
마리아, 자네의 결정으로
이 살인범을 잡게 되었어
Maria,it wasyour decision making
that led to his captureand arrest,
그리고 자백을 하게 만들어서
모두들 한시름 놓게 됐지
and you madeall our lives easier
by getting the bastardto confess.
I'm just doing my job.
제가 할 일을 했습니다
It feels good to bepraising your police
work instead of your politicsfor a change.
자네의 정책 변화보다
경찰 일에 칭찬을 하게 돼서 기쁘네
공식 성명을 발표해야 해서요
We need to makean official comment.
Don't worry.I'll keep it short.
걱정 마세요, 짧게 끝낼 테니
I'm just heading downstairs
now for the press conference.
아래층에 기자회견이 있거든요
The press conferenceis over.
기자회견은 끝났네
Oh,and,uh,don't worry.
걱정 말게, 짧게 끝냈으니
I kept it short.
지금 농담하세요!?
You got to be fucking kidding me.
That was my bust.
제가 잡은 놈이에요
This is my department.
여긴 내 관할이야
적어도 제 공로는 인정하셨겠죠?
Did you at leastgive me credit?
Yes.I just gave it to you.
그럼, 방금 전에 해 줬잖아
안 듣고 있었나?
Haven't you been listening?
Ever since harry's
death,I've been alone...
아버지가 죽은 이후로 난 늘 혼자였다
but now,for the first time...
하지만 처음으로 난 혼자라는 생각이다
I feel alone.
How long you need
with the prisoner?
죄수와 얼마나 같이 있어야 되죠?
같이 있을 수 있는 만큼요
As long as I can get.
Jeremy is gone,
제레미가 갔다
닐 페리도 곧 시스템이라는
무덤으로 사라져 갈 것이다
and neil perry will soon vanish
into the catacombs of the system.
그에게 질문할 것이 아주 많다
I have so many questions for him.
How did he discover my secrets?
어떻게 내 비밀을 알아냈는지
What was his message to me?
그가 남긴 메세지는 무엇인지
He's been in my home,
그는 내 집에 왔었다
my photos...my life.
내 사진들, 내 삶, 그는 나를 알고 있다
He knows me.
Now I need to know him...
이제는 내가 그를 알아야겠다
to connect face-to-face
얼굴을 마주하고 알아 가야겠다
before he's beyond my reach forever.
그가 내 손이 닿지 않는 곳으로
가기 전에, 영원히
Hi.
안녕
Who the fuck are you?
넌 또 누구야?
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET-鬼柰훙珙
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
디시인사이드 미국드라마 갤러리
딕테이션/한글번역 : 에스뷰
한글교정 : 글그린이™
싱크편집 : jimmy